Biel Serrano Sanchez

Overview

Hello! I am Biel, a .NET Backend Developer with more than 4 years of experience.

I love programming, video games, music and illustration.

Backend Developer

Contact

<u>bielsesa@gmail.com</u> www.astronautpotato.com

(+34)649609347 Vilafranca del Penedes, Barcelona, 08720 (They/Them)

Skills

SOLID principles

Agile

SCRUM

TDD & DDD

WPF & WinForms

SQL and NoSQL

.NET Development and C#

Git Version Control

REST API Development

Unity3D (personal experience)

Next.js (personal experience)

I graduated with two higher certificates focused on multi-platform and web application development, and at some point, I would like to finish my Computer Science degree online.

I believe in curiosity and high adaptability as motivations to always move forward.

For any inquiries, do not hesitate to contact me by e-mail. Thank you!

Experience

Backend Developer @ ERNI, S.L. | 03/2023 - Current

Development and product care of pharmaceutical software, MedTech sector.

Participate in code reviews, demos to POs and in the design of new features. Agile and SCRUM.

Technologies used: .NET Framework, WPF, Oracle SQL Server, XML, HL7 standard, RabbitMQ, WCF

Junior Software Developer @ DIR INFORMATICA BCN, S.L. | 02/2021 - 03/2023

Product care and migration of an ERP specialized for the bakery sector. Constant contact with stakeholders and clients to better meet their needs. Agile and SCRUM.

Education

Escola Jesuites El Clot

- Certificate of Higher Education of Multi-platform Application Development (Big Data and IoT Specialization)
- Certificate of Higher Education of Web Application Development

Universitat Politecnica de Catalunya

Computer Science Degree (1 and ½ years, unfinished)

Languages

Spanish - Native

Catalan - Native

English - B2 Level

Japanese – Beginner Level

Technologies used: .NET Core 6 and .NET Framework 4.8 and 4.7 with C#, VB6 and SQL Server, RabbitMQ

Junior Software Developer @ STEP LOGISTICA, S.L. | 02/2019 - 06/2020

Development of internal tools and POCs.

Technologies used: WPF and WinForms, .NET Framework 4.6, 4.7 and 4.8, C#, JavaScript, JSON